

CONTACT

WHATSAPP = +62 85157474504

EMAIL = rabipraya@gmail.com

LinkedIn = Rayi Abipraya

Address = Kabupaten Bekasi,

Jawa Barat

EDUCATION

Test Aplikasi Kamu Bootcamp QA automation (2023)

Sanbercode Januari (2022) Web Developer

Back End Developer Glints Academy Batch 12 April 2021 - Agustus 2021

STMIK Indo Daya Suvana Completed 72 credit 2015 - 2018

Language

English - Advance Bahasa Indonesia - Native Speaker

Rayi Abipraya

QUALITY ASSURANCE ENGINEER

Summary

Like to learn new things and have great enthusiasm, especially in the IT field. As a QA, i like to make test management like create test plan, test cases, test suites and trials.

Expertise

- Cypress
- Selenium python
- Postman
- Laravel
- CSS

- ClickUp
- Jira
- Agile Framework
- Scrum Framwork

Experience

IT FREELANCER

PT KHARISMA TAUFAN PUTRA (2019)

- Create the company's official website
- Maintenance official website for process regruitment
- Connecting praspective workers to related companies

BACK END DEVELOPER

PT Codehouse Teknologi Oase (Internship)

- Problem solving some code
- learn new knowledge such a other language
- Helping developer team develop, especially bug fixing

QUALITY ASSURANCE

PT Codehouse Teknologi Oase (Full time) Des 2021 - Aug 2023

QUALITY ASSURANCE

PT PINDUIT TEKNOLOGI INDONESIA (FREELANCE) Nov 2022 - Jan 2023

- Identify, record, document thoroughly and track bugs
- Develop and apply testing processes for new and existing products to meet client needs
- Monitor debugging process results
- Stay up-to-date with new testing tools and test strategies

Portfolio

GLINTS FINAL PROJECT

BILLER APP

GLINTS MINI PROJECT

MOVIE REVIEW

SANBERCODE Project Katakami • Project Video

https://bit.lu/3CiJjqT

• Git lab repository https://bit.lu/3usD9SG

• API Documentation

https://bit.ly/3Ch73LY

• Git lab repository https://bit.ly/3CiGt55

 Git lab repositoru https://gitlab.com/bangiim/kat Bidding Apps a-kami

Project

From Companies

CMK

E-Procurement Desember 2021 - June is a web for process of requisitioning, ordering and purchasing goods and services online. It is a <u>business-to-</u> business process.

CMK

E-Approval February 2022 - June 2022

is a web for Approving Documents for internal purposes

ADIRA

May 2022 - June 2022

web and App for Bidding the vehicle to be auctioned

ADELE ROYALTY

Jewellery Apps May 2022

member Adelle (jewellery store)

web and App for Royalty

MIZORA JEWELRY

Mizora Web & Admin dashboard September 2022

web for customer see some product and buy jewelry from Mizora

PT.PII (PERSERO)

E-Procurement Desember 2022

is a web for process of requisitioning, ordering and purchasing goods and services online. It is a business-tobusiness process.

PT PINDUIT **TEKNOLOGI INDONESIA**

November

digital financial websites and financial services and comprehensive business development support

MIZORA JEWELRY

Mizora Web September 2022 web for customer see some product and buy jewelry from Mizora